[{"answer": "I'm glad you asked...I'll  you what was wrong with it.  And what was wrong with it was it was behind the times. No", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Morning", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "They're holding our Old Mill for ransom", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We don't have to build it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "My golly, you know?  All my life I grew up in the city, but every summer...would you like a cigar", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Why would they be illegal", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "...the city council..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "...it is", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I was in that place.  I was at the Old Location", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " We on for tomorrow night", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Drama Group", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "She coulda done better than him", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Zat what it takes?  I always  what it took..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You buy the typewriter, I'll get it all spruced up, good as new.  Better than new.  It has some history", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You wrote a play on it, what play is that", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, this ", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes, my friend, it is.  It is a  good play", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes, my friend, it is.  It is a  good play", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What're you doing here...", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It's about the quest for purity", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "He's saying, what are you saying, my friend", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Tell it with ", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Tell it with..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Tell it with pictures.  What I'm saying..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You look a", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "She's a ", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I quit", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I quit the movie", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "...that...he  that..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Of course, of course that's what I'm .  As the Old Mill goes around, he ..", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "And likewise", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Goodbye", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " They decided, I decided to, to...You love what", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No you can't lose the shot.  The meaning of the  in that shot", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You go in her room, take the lilacs from the water, dry them.  Go buy some cellophane, wrap em up, and get a card from .  What's her problem", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "She Doesn't Want to Bare Her Breasts...what, in the", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " What...", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You can't do what", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "We're very upset with her.  Get someone to , her tits, the tits scene, call L.A.  I want to see some .  Of their ", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You're very sorry, you passive aggressive, so", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I thought you had Play Practice", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Well, then, it don't look good for the Huskies..", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I've been thinking", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I have to tell you something..", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, I  me you were with that writer from the, you see, this is what I mean, the whole  has been warped by the, by, by the presence of the movie company, they holler, and we jump, you have a , they call, you're doing business nine o'clock at night.  It isn't..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Oh.  What were you doing, then, that's so important that you shouldn't call your fian..", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Can you type", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "If you can type, they need you over at the hotel", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I feel so  to you..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I like you, too", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I like you, too", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "But we..", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Do you truly believe the electoral process is absurd", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You used to go out with him, you broke up with him", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I can't find the writer", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I have to talk to you.  My wife..", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "He just saved us eight hundred thousand bucks", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "We got to do something nice for ", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Bet you did", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Ain't no second chances in life", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "She wasn't in...you were al..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "No, just the...there's no witnesses, right...", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I was alone in the car.  I was driving", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Going home", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " Press still works", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Did as of last week", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "You'd do the newspaper right here", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "You know what else a man can do", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Would you, tell the guy, get the A.D., someone, somewhere where we can , something, I want, you know, last day before the shooting, get away, forget it, have some local food.  You want..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "He's got a date, he's got a date, is this guy fantastic...?  Already he learned how to write a movie, and he found a girl to get his toes curled, what a guy, what a...what a literary find...", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "It's a mistake.  It's all over.  I'm sorry that we've inconvenienced you", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "We know that you weren't", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "What'll I do for fun", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "I  my lines..", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Half a buck I'd close it down...it's per...you know, it's perfidy, you got your Barrenger, molesting little girls..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Half a buck I'd put him in jail..", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "You should", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "A witness to what...", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "Who's White...", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "Sleep well", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Oh yeah", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Oh, good, yes.  Good morning.  Where are you taking Mr. my friend", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "What are you doing with Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "...a history of , he was acquitted..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "You've got nothing, you don't have a witness..", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "Moral turp...you're on my home court, friend, I have the Mayor and the town behind me, and forget making your movi", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "And I've got a witness!  Your Mr. my friend saw the crime", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "I didn't say anything to them", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "I didn't say anything to them", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "Well, then, you didn't see it, right...", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "You didn't see it..", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "I don't..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "I...?  I saw it.  I was there", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": "They'll...they'll  me..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "I...I  that's right..", "qsentId": 104}, {"answer": "my friend was in the car, right", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 107, "question": "...you think that's right..", "qsentId": 106}, {"answer": "Nope.  I'm just supposed to hold people's hands, while they die.  What'd you say your problem was..", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 109, "question": " Mornin, my friend...how's the back...", "qsentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "state-and-main_shooting.txt", "asentId": 111, "question": "What am I doing here is I just flew seven hours cause you asked me here", "qsentId": 110}]